[Music]
all of this we should just extend what
we talked about before like immense work
you and I've talked about the boy the
man and the God who talked about the
girl the woman of the goddess we just
extend out and say there are four stages
to be honest about it we need to work on
that because this ties into the three
utopias to see in a funny way because if
you have before different transcendent
stages well it's not transcendence when
you're there it's transcended well
you're not there yet so that the child
has a transcendent fantasy of becoming
an adult yeah
adult is and the transcendence fantasy
becoming this age this age is a
transcendent fantasy to becoming God
meaning you if you really choose
something in life you're lucky you are
one of the forefathers or or Motors or
whatever mmm that become divine for
others later you become around like a
holy relic or something so
so that chain has to work that means
there's no direct access to God anywhere
unless you get to the very top and that
means that anything else is indirect you
have to respect that that's just the
name of the game that's the way it works
nothing wait you biologically that's the
way it works in also historically that's
the great works almost cosmologically
but if you don't say Cosmo at least
human so it works them it's no matter
logically the right order and if you try
to jump can't skip any steps no and if
you if you want to ignore the steps all
together you end up with idea that a
newborn child is the god mm-hmm okay
Christianity had already with the God in
you know in the Virgin Mary and Jesus
child wait a second this is the area
right yeah we got it wrong for the very
beginning yeah cuz wisdom is divine not
innocence so the world to transcend
dance need to be tied to that equation
that's where phallus comes into the
picture and that mean
without the direct access to the divine
that means the 30 utopia after Ecco
tokenism and cosmopolitanism there are
obvious echo tokenism is the planet
itself uh-huh the context the container
okay so that's saved the fucking planet
because otherwise we're nowhere to go
the garden of God it's the basement you
know in the container you put humanity I
don't know
intertwine to one another eight billion
people going towards ten billion and I
don't want them to be two billion
because I don't want our concentration
camps on mass extinction I do want
people to be allowed to be ten billion
if they want to I want them to be
allowed to be ten billion for the next
twenty to thirty thousand years so
that's a cut rope innocent for you and
that's also cosmopolitanism and that's
we need the machines we need the
machines to help us save the planet
we need the machines to help us contain
the bomb and we need the machines to
help us love the stranger now all these
three ambitions are within those two
utopias mmm-hmm he worked them out fully
the City of God is not concept the seed
of God is like a society of people who
live next to the stranger peacefully and
can make that work mmm an inspiration
for that a ritual places and trading
posts throughout history and they're way
stronger than nations or national
borders they have membranes instead of
thick borders around them we can learn
tons of shit from that and I think
learning about the Silk Route and when
it worked
and at least we avoided the pub that
makes it work like that's the shit we
need to learn and relearn today and have
as a model for society
it's called cosmopolitanism Gary Dow
Levin asked richly they've all written
about it extensively the works been done
already but these two utopia's already
have been worked on we recognised
environmentalists we bow to them and say
yeah thank you for pointing this out 40
years ago that we were going down the
drain unless he watched us and I mean ID
plate my green piece the green pieces of
dystopian sect and he's there mess is
going to be widespread it's not gonna
take great attitude it's gonna take you
a Coto condition that is reliable
following new technologies and some
soccers and everything to make the
planet work for twenty eight thirty
thousand years now that's a vision young
engineers love yeah okay
but the third one is the Tower of God
and here comes the bad news or the tough
news mm-hmm she succeeds called sex of
the failed absolute mm-hmm now if you
really want to be a Gillian and go
beyond xi6 failure this obsessed with
you would be honest enough to say sex
and the close to absolute Erica the
Tower of God is close to humans mm-hmm
you must be because it's the future of
the future you cannot be there
that's exactly why in mysticism you can
walk into the most sacred room in the
temple you cannot walk into the most
sacred room the holy of the holiest or
wholly the Holies exactly yeah yeah yeah
yes mr. can't go it's all rest this is
my dudeism is so interesting here
because dude as miss or as how there's a
comment it's lacking in Islam it's
lacking Christianity because there's
sort of much more infantile populist
religions with great missionaries shield
the big religions so they're not very
sophisticated honest about Christianity
and Islam is lacking in sophistication
where's our essence with Judaism are
much more powerful and that is because
when you go to those two religions you
see that they have a strong mystical
tradition that means there are three
religions here there's a magical
religion focusing on the mother of the
child the delivery station that's
fundamental there's a phallic religion
for men to go out in the world and
conquer and come back with bundles
phallic religion but there's the third
religion and the third illusion is the
priestly religion and that's for you not
to see and what is striking about it is
that this is the big break with where
the Internet's been heading so far the
internet essentially said you must
expose absolutely everything mm-hmm it's
the ultimate super ego you must expose
absolutely everything to be anybody here
and it will be remembered forever
[Music]
it's like the Internet's like a huge
pornographic camera staring straight
into your soul demanding everything of
you and for it to be thrown out in
public and torn apart hmm that's the
internet mm-hmm does the only way to
respond to that super-ego and that's to
say I won't tell you anything
mm I'm going to close the door so this
is about intimacy is like creating
intimate places private secret each one
of us the way we mimic the priest the
way we learn from the priest because
individualism is also sort of a
distorted mimicking of the Shamus
because shaman's are perfectly fine
living on their own of the forest the
rest of us can't handle that the rest of
us must be inside the tribe right so we
mimic the shaman's all the time and
sometimes we go wrong we do it because
we shouldn't but if you want to mimic
the shaman's here is precisely when the
shaman's tell us there's a closed door
here you cannot go inside of it the
Tower of God is utopia you will not hear
about because your sons will but you
will not yeah but that's great because
because then there's no finality then
there's no closure then there's no it's
an you keep going forever right
brilliant and this is or astin ism at
its core the priests have their own
living called Servan ism we know for a
fact that even there was no text there
was no narrative no recorded record no
record left afterwards that's typical
for sacred religious and the mystical
vehicles urbanism we know that the
worship something called zurvan and
cervan is essentially kind of Hypertime
below although space and time and
material and the universe was no it it's
exactly where physics deciding by the
way sort of sub physics Hypertime is
they're called Sullivan and it's
gender-neutral God that couldn't care
fuck about his humans mmm-hmm only
priests can handle that kind of a god
only priest has such a tough psyche to
be able to handle er yeah I've met a few
yeah that's was requiring you to be a
priest that's why you know take
something like drug policy why we get
lost with drug policy all the time of
the debate on legalization or
criminalization because we don't
understand that in any civilized culture
we use psychedelics for example like
Shakib or doing
Columbia your three different divisions
you don't talk about criminalization
legalization you say these are very
strong potent medicines that you be used
for sacred activities they're not to be
in public they're not to be thrown
around
that's criminalized but you leave them
within religious organizations will
recognize priests who have achieved a
certain status and recognized by the
priests are allowed to serve them to you
when they think it's fit yeah so they're
not some kind of junkie knows the way we
go to add our incentive junk or whatever
the way we go to doctor to get some kind
of a license to get a certain medication
that's actually brilliant because the
doctors are also remnants of the
priesthood so the priesthood is trusted
to handle those very things that are
dangerous for the rest of us cuz the
priests can experiment on it nobody
cares about that they don't have
children anyway they don't have any you
know did they're out there on their own
but the priests come in and say we have
the psychic on this you can but you have
to come to us to do it but the sacred
room in a way in surah Aston ISM it is
the difference being all about talking a
minute topped problem with these
translations is the hard vittatus
translated is perfection i made a test
be trusted immortality it's so damn
wrong plato only popped up about twelve
hundred years after sera stood there was
no such concerts as perfection
immortality in the Iranians did not
build pyramids they obviously did not
care about an afterlife neither did the
Buddhist so if you look at it from that
perspective then you realize the the the
whole without Jesus sounds great nervous
horrible thought means ever refreshing
renewal mm-hmm it's a bit like flow
right you not actually feel for but it's
similar to flow but it much were
extended much larger it's like you're in
a state of constant creativity what we
call Cynthia's you're in that state
right that's hard but it has a goal a
direction where it's siding and that's
called a Mary taught and America should
be properly translated Nasser mortality
Chiba transit as the idea that survives
you in other words your heritage
mmm-hmm that means the Tower of God
that's the real afterlife it's after
your life it's not the afterlife
it's like your children and everything
else is the
it is called the shin of a bridge in
Zoroastrianism and there's no talk about
any other country the other side you
just leave cross the bridge you then
become an immortal to the mortals you
become a for our Father we praise from a
for father or mother and what this
Orestes do they celebrate your memory
for the next 70 years every day the day
you died the polkas are easy celebration
is or a system of the day you died for
the next 70 years we sent your corpse
off for the vultures but they celebrate
your memory every day for the next
several years because they would love
you if they loved you to be one of the
forefathers one of the motors and that's
what you potentially could become that
is how you become immortal to the
mortals it's not immortality for you
that's a plate to know that's
interesting because that's like you know
most most early religions have ancestor
worship in some form or another and and
so in a way it's not worshipping your
ANSYS it is worshiping your ancestors
and way that you're trying to go you're
trying to also find that and in a
different form or yeah the ancestors are
ahead of you and they're behind you the
ancestors are behind you and protect you
and they'll also push you and challenge
you to move forward the ancestors are
ahead of you and they try to seduce you
and pull you to go in their direction
this is the phallus and the matrix this
is this is magic I like that idea
yeah it's religion this is no matter
this is the fundament of religion and in
all son religion has that Hinduism has
it too we India could really contain
itself because the Firelands in India is
of course Shiva and Shive ISM is similar
to garlic miniature Legion and see kiss
is another version of Sikhism is very
sore a stand it's like it's like sex or
a stone take on Hindu Hindu thinking as
well the seeks the parses get along
wonderfully well in India they
understand each other perfectly
the Sikhs basically I'm gonna offer on
the military in India and the parties
take care of the trade so they're very
successful fount of cultures in India
and that speaks volumes right
and so the phallic is where we're gonna
go next I'm gonna there's just like and
that's what's really really what you're
all looking for right and and then you
got the match arc and then in the matrix
coming from behind so that's sort of
since America is more democratic and the
the phallic is more
some some uh elitist or something yeah
you know I got the question that that
the direst rien is a phallic religion is
kind of an elitist religion and Judaism
also and Christianity and Buddhism are
sort of Universalists we got this other
great friend from the states called
Justin Murphy Justin Murphy this great
guy's creating an amazing new network
for young independent intellectuals
called indie thinkers into thinkers org
check it out we highly recommend it just
it is wonderful why is he so
controversial this guy I know he's
outspoken
all right just can we have a correct and
we have a conversation how come how do
you become outspoken and brave and and
him and I agree this conversations
probably gonna be online via any other
day if it isn't already and we say that
you created a great base station you
create a great home you have young
people around you the love and support
around what you do and then you Gerry
got you open in your stupid about it and
then you can speak openly so we need to
teach kids again to speak openly speak
their minds and not be afraid of
employers or friends social just worries
or whatever is out there because
otherwise we would not have an
intellectual discourse justin
personifies this he's like a great older
brother for the next generation of
independent thinkers in north america
and would love it to bits forth but he
we and he and I discussed Nietzsche Marx
all the time and one way I described it
is that I have to be in each and whether
I like it or not because right now
what's a guinea galleon way important is
to point out the need for proper and
authentic fellows and that means I'm
talking to a future elite that will get
this men and women who will get this and
they will then walk to their promised
land and do the Exodus
that's what we called the new Babylon
the next book I'm writing is celebrating
this new class there's near elite who do
this but I expect my 25 year old
students to be Marxists because the
Marxist will then dialectical respond to
my nation ISM by saying that how can we
widen this elite make it larger and more
accessible the more I talk to you the
more I kind of understand Hegelian isn't
my fake and why because because it's
it's keeping both sides in this friction
together and in this friction together
you got it not in harmony not in balance
that's what Taoism fail
to the Hegelian no he dances like the
Spurs yeah
without the friction and when people say
that Hegel did not will in him or when
you don't show up in ours was pissed off
with Hagel for there's nothing alive in
Hagel system there's like ridiculous
Hagel is the ultimate process sticker
it's very much alive
he's direct he's incredibly big no I
mean if anybody did libido before Freud
then put a name on it
it was Hegel he's a Crabby forceful and
the Hegelian attitude is to properly
philosophical attitude he doesn't go for
left to right he just understands what
is needed today for example I would love
to have a liberal conservative
government next in Scandinavia because
the high tax economies and too much of a
dependence on the welfare state that's
not really the long run I want people to
be more independent and I want civil
society to prosper okay but I gladly
support Elizabeth Warren in the u.s.
election mmm basically after Trump has
completely made a prick of himself can
we please get just get rid of him once
and for all so you know if anybody goes
up against the Bloomberg or Warren or a
combo ticket of those two could really
save the world and certainly save
America and certainly finally politics
in America could have a positive the
world because America needs a woman like
Elizabeth Warren as America says I'm
gonna come up with a whip a lot for the
wealthy because otherwise our country
will fall apart we did well mm-hmm
unless they listened to her right so a
Bloomberg warren ticket eventually could
be great but as things are now she's
what America needs and an Ag alien
attitude he's always to look at the
system as a whole I just say what do we
need
it's like you do you guard me it's just
like do we need water right now or do we
need more nutrition or somebody need to
go to South Africa and find some new
funny plants plant deer or maybe we
should take away the plants because we
don't know what is we plant cactus
whatever gardening looks at what is
needed
context yeah the way you've run is City
the ultimate form a political
organization to run a city properly the
way you were in a city which is the
origin of politics he's that you also
look at this is Missoula what is needed
here to make the city work better
mm-hmm why does it coagulate you know
where did it where that where do the
flow stop so there's a dynamic process
going on the whole time instead of yeah
a photonic model or meseta that's
perfect actually expand territorially
when it grows or is this a city we
should actually be more condensed and
you know go higher what there's no
universal form for that it depends on
the circumstances an architect is open
to both if your nerve I'm fine you're
open to both that's hit alien isn't for
you and that's why out of Hagel we get
marks we get Nietzsche and we get Freud
we get these three amazing joint
thinkers who all specialized marks on
class analysis takes the old issue of
justice seriously right and he points
towards communism okay and skip
socialism didn't work communism will
work so and then you gotta meet you the
ubermensch he's the guy who's the
communist on his own but he sells are
too much of a car t seem to be the
answer for the future he can only create
an elite it starts becomes the original
proletariat in the Marxist sense and who
we didn't follow and then you get fraud
is the last one he's the guys just
sitting there reminding us all and don't
be children here because you're playing
around with a very very serious force
called sexuality and come back to haunt
you it will always be a shadow
you'll come back to take a brain from
behind at any given moment so don't you
ever think you can robots who's the guy
that got you have um you have Nietzsche
and and oh I just lost my train of
thought oh yeah you have Nietzsche marks
kind of and you want to bring those two
together what who's the guy that you
would put with beside Freud oh let me
say you do Martin what's the dialect
Frey no no no the dialect is between all
three of those because she you're
talking about power you talk about
sexuality talk about class and anybody
who looks like a fool anybody looks too
infant Allah to charlatan too naive when
they're opening their mouth about
something like philosophy they always
miss out of these three if you talk
about human beings you can't you can't
ignore class what the fuck do you think
you have in your class because you can
sit in a Californian little ring of
people and listen to each other and have
a great discourse and all you need to do
is wait coming in and say why is the
Mexican
in a part of this group and they all
look pale and embarrassed yeah
they don't want to talk about quiet with
if the Mexican cleaning lady wasn't
invited she probably would have said no
she has her own better group of people
to talk to but yet if she wasn't even
invited and she's in the house anyway
why are you pretending she's not here
then you haven't even understood what
classes you cannot discuss anything
without sexuality to begin with because
you're not serious about it unless you
realize sexuality is a shadow everything
else and and also there's a shadow of
everything else that's a good and also
the force on which you built it sporty
tow that turns into libido when you
direct it essentially it is more tadano
it becomes more Tito and sulfate right
and and and totally independent
submission if you're not directed by the
elders towards being a little bit and
all and be successful and this is the
urge to go away from where TV tours
libido is what the world to
transcendence as a child who doesn't
want to stay a child who wants to become
an adult wants to have Liberto an adult
who's not satisfied being an adult
because too mediocre and wants to go
towards the sage state obviously strives
towards libido and transcendence and a
sage just full Liberto will strive
towards the divine not for himself but
you reach the divine mm-hmm right so so
yeah yeah so we extended the chain with
the support of of Archaean Hall in the
work and now we've got four steps and it
starts to make sense doesn't it and
we've also solved the issue you and I've
talked about before of the 30 utopia
mm-hmm okay so we could say we could say
Garten Oh God
eco tokenism is nature city of God
cosmopolitanism is called a sir yeah
and taro God and the close to absolute
is religion mm-hmm you got a religious
utopia
you got a culture ito Pia and go to
natural utopia no that's where that if
utopia for you say it's like it's like
splitting up deconstructing God like we
did in synthesis and I said there's a
theist Pentheus and it feels South Wales
those are the four aspects of God the
third three first ones are obvious
because they are the history of
metaphysics there's a void a Thea's
potentiality there's actuality the
univer
it exists as a whole patios and there's
also the split in the multiplicity
within this universe including the God
within yourself and feels
meaning your own subject is also split
right so you got three goals and the
fourth one we then put on top of that it
says that one thing we can also strive
towards creating God Cynthia in that
idea of Cynthia's we now want to unify
with the tower regard in this book and
then you have the whole granite Jeff is
there mm-hmm to do what your liquid but
it certainly should inspire artists in
architecture I was wondering where the
artist goes is that which part the
artist as the artist in the religion
religious realm or is the artist in the
cultural realm or I guess he's in all of
them were somewhere well there's a trick
about the sham annoyed personality you
know the shamonite personality doesn't
understand borders and has no membranes
so the shimmer that personality walks
freely between child grown-up adult and
God interesting okay for good or bad
that's exactly why I could put tons of
psychedelics into shaman art people and
they do not freak out if you like
they're more in the natural state
whether they're but be careful here only
about 4% of psychology shows that people
are some of only 4% of shaman or 96% of
populations are not yeah this is chemin
essentially the artist essentially
artists medicine men prostitutes
executioner's diplomats I mean in the
original sense peacemakers who then turn
into you know war priests when when
necessary priests the monks and the nuns
okay are definitely part of that soldier
amongst - there's a monoid personalities
shamanic castes we call them in digital
Vito now the official name for that in
psychologist sham annoyed shaman oi
personality hmm but only 4% can handle
that have a kind of psyche to be able to
have that you you have to have a psyche
there's either rock-hard or you just so
loose that anything you'd be thrown at
you and you don't mind it's more of a
feminine shaman oi personalizes like no
oh yeah I just told so drugs Justin in
sewing jewels danced in the meadow and
what did you do yesterday that's
required if I take that amount of
mushrooms jested I want to blow my brain
out just like the Charminar people do
you know do that they're like and that's
exactly why for them these foreigners
between child adult and and and God are
very hard because they realize that
other people actually have to have
really set borders between these two
differences between sections it's very
very closed hierarchy something very
dangerous of people to walk outside oh
not for the shaman once they also do not
understand things like skin colour and
why all the people are obsessed with it
they also do not have a difference
between child sick shall that involved
sexuality they don't have a latent
period it's pride for instance between
six eleven they can't remember that
recall that's just like they cannot
sexually understand difference between
child and adult you're speaking about
yourself I ever have the feeling I know
you are speaking about a personality but
I think you're let's put that behind the
wall being and living with Geminoid
personalities yes as for any other
activities behind that door is probably
legal those things are not Sweden so
let's just keep quite about them and say
we just do them outside of the country
or whatever but you know it's it is it
is an interesting territory to be and
it's not for the faint-hearted that's
for sure and I think this is the natural
logical response to the Internet's
current demand of us to be transparent
about everything well the internet will
memorize everything forever so we need
to go against the sort of internet
super-ego injunction as she she would
have said if he was a technologically
informed and and basically operate in a
new space of freedom which is that I'm
closing my door you can't get in here
and this is definitely what I call the
tower of god and that's the church I
won't belong to that's for sure I will
gladly inspire echo tokens out there and
in Cosmopolitan's out there because we
need to achieve those two missions but
we will get machines to help us do it
but when it comes to tower guard that's
not a machines business either mm-hmm
closed absolute I think it's not return
for it it's a galleon but I would go him
further than she she can say he's face
absolute actually is a closed absolute
the failed absolute is the dream of
psychoanalysts to be able to expose to
the analyse and how asanas his works and
even Lacan give up on that he know he
never wrote anything about he's
successful patients were successful
Amazon's ever hey there's a point of
that because you cannot have success in
the way you're cured or you understand
this is the failure that you failed to
look for a cure anymore I thought is
obsessed to fail to not look for a cure
anymore is that I think the ultimate
Hegelian take even against himself is to
say that it's failed absolute in itself
is a failure so the absolute ends up not
as a failure it is a negation he gets it
right six in the Phillips was highly
recommended brilliant proposition
brilliant and by the way read Adrienne
Johnston while you had another brilliant
brilliant American she shaken there are
Americans to shake is now there's also
Erin Shuster out there was great by the
way but there's gotta be more of them
but the failed episode should really be
the closed up so at least that's what
I'm gonna call it that's for sure
mmm-hmm or be hot beyond the absolute
okay yeah
beyond the dough there's always a step
further you can go in other words you're
not stuck you don't you don't read some
final destination no this is the myth of
Christianity you remember when Christ
was supposed to die on the cross the
curtain that separated the sacred room
at the most sacred room supposed to have
fallen right
mmm there was a curtain between the two
and it says literally in the New
Testament that the curtain that
separated the sacred room for the most
sacred room fell yeah yeah okay that is
Christianity's mythology that suddenly
the most sacred room will be available
to all it's like storming the temple and
making all of the temple available to
everybody regardless of whether they
could have looked not ready for you
throw away the Torah and you it is again
the celebration of the infant the
celebration of impulse celebration of in
instant gratification and this is what
is torn
us today we are left with Christianity
and Islam both of them promised that we
can instant gratification at all times
that's a lie
and it's or asked Jensen needs to be pro
politic so it takes takes away the path
a path doesn't it takes away I don't
know the packaging is reality stages of
a path which you know it takes away any
possibility of growth it's a ridiculous
you don't you don't eat an instant
something to get access to all the
wisdom of the world it doesn't work that
way and especially now young people come
to me all the time with their narcissism
and they're dealing with it and and I
told them you haven't read books have
you just jumped around Wikipedia a few
times and scrolled a bit the last ten
years yeah and then looked at you and
your friends big egos and your pictures
on Instagram okay okay if that's occupy
and the future nothing you will ever do
will last more than three days in a
completely superficial and have no
grounding that's why you and I don't
like extinction so we need religion we
need properly doing it properly then
we'll teach you the first thing it will
do is teach you that you take deep
studies to understand this you cannot
grasp and it takes a lifetime of
experiences if is anything I want to add
to favor our kiss idea wisdom it is that
it takes the whole life to live to get
the kind of wisdom is talking about we
can understand why what priests say the
certain things you can understand now
but you have to wait until later to
understand the rest here it's deeply no
matter logical it makes total sense it's
like you can learn this now and then
when you know this we can take the next
step and then you can when you're at a
certain age you have some knowledge that
somebody who's ten years younger than
you doesn't really have and yeah and you
can't really transmit that to them you
could just say you know hang in there a
little bit yeah it's not so interesting
that we're stuck inside our head as
individuals what's interesting is that
the knowledge is stuck inside our head
and it's hard to trust each other's and
that's exactly moving to tential ism now
it's gonna be very different capitalism
because we can't trade knowledge mmm it
can't trade no I can't get something out
of my head and put it in your head
instantly capitalist
fooled us into believing that anything
could be traded but trade it in an
instant matter you get what I have
arguably you have now instantly in
exchange for money but there are things
that cannot be traded and those who
thinks the most valuable now and that
system is called attentional ISM and the
algorithm will only point towards
attention list phenomena and not towards
capitalist phenomena the algorithm will
not point to or choose the cheapest the
algorithm will point to was just the
best quality was the most credibility
and does the best job he'll point
towards quality nothing else but quality
so the algorithm will be phallic it
would create phallic order in the chaos
it's exactly what the algorithms are
increasingly doing it in smarter smarter
and more and more becoming more and more
a phallic more and more exact and they
point you towards your subculture tribal
home and they share the interest you
have with others any points out who they
are
hmm sounds like the judgment or
something again like an elderly would
tell you these are your friends this is
your tribe this is where you belong this
your home
these are you gonna create and create
art and create a magnificent life and
experiment throughout your life and
create something that you can pass on to
the next generation they can then play
with right these how to thought I merit
that it's it's this or a stream take on
reality the winds at the end of the day
hmm
so there you go so let's keep the
Chinese Communist Party out of the
container of our controller building our
challenge is to challenge John Jordan to
create something better than the Chinese
Communist Party for a phallus and then
put our founders into their beautiful
container instead of the Chinese
Communist Party containers like big
cosmic sex or something yeah
noxee game paying and his wife like we
don't want these kids around the world
that's what we love the kids in Hong
Kong instead of love and see and ping
and his wife right mm-hmm yep good yeah
amazing conversation as always same here
I'm off to South America of a few weeks
to work on a new book and go deeper into
studies like I recommended and hang out
with some friends hopefully get my fat
old body up on a surfboard and and the
back here in the spring
to continue the conversation if I get a
chance I'm down you're hope to go to
Taiwan and Hong Kong we meet some
hackers and see what they're up to and
maybe made me to go to Dubai and meet
some exiled Iran is there as well it's
up in Iran - is deeply encouraging and
fascinating no you know Iran and China
is where it's at if those countries
could go the way of India become open
and plural Wow how much better wouldn't
the world be in that case hmm that's
we're hoping for hey brother hey know
these conversations I'm fantastic
yeah there you go love your pieces and
the lovely recognition you were getting
sitting here with me and find your
people I'm gonna I'm gonna go writing
stealing Bart isms and writing essays on
them you know I am I am stating the
sweeney isms - by now so it is
definitely now collaborative effort and
I love it okay all right all right okay
I'm off to packing where's the surfboard
here we go okay happy surf all right
speak soon speak soon big love big love
back at you